[Music]
[Applause]
part
two number seven the files have all been
submitted haven't they a yes about 2
hours ago B I'll submit my application
then C Mr Peters wants to see
them number eight I recommend applying
for a job at hermine
Consulting a a low-level employee there
b that's what I'm planning to do c no
you didn't recommend
that number nine how long do you intend
to wait for Mr
Schnell a I've known him for years B
several months from now C until the
workday
ends number 10 what time is the flight
supposed to land a let me check the
schedule B we're landing in San
Francisco C it's flight TR
492 number 11 shouldn't you submit the
application form at once a actually I
already did B apply it to the surface C
yes he has very good
form number 12 do you happen to know who
the head accountant is a he works in the
accounting department B get ahead by
working hard C his name is Fred Marshall
number
13 can you please file these documents
for me a there's the file cabinet B
sorry but I'm too busy now C no they
haven't been
documented number
14 where did Jenny put the stapler after
she finished using it a the Staples are
in the draw B she left it on the counter
C I'm sitting at my desk
now number
15 how much does it cost to purchase a
box of
paper a I bought some paper B 5,000
sheets per box C I'm not quite sure
number
16 there appears to be a mistake on this
report a why am I mistaken B didn't he
report it C what's wrong with
it number
17 could you please send me the
itinerary by
email a I'll do that after lunch B
that's my email address C it's our
schedule for the
conference number
18 why don't we meet Mr Richardson at
the restaurant after work a I'd like a
menu please B no he doesn't work there C
I already have plans
tonight number
19 was that Mr Murphy's Bus who just
called him on the phone a his boss is
Miss thunderson B no it was a client of
his C call me at 4074994695
number
21 when did Miss Jackson send the
contract to be
signed a by Courier I believe B both
your name and hers c 2 or 3 days
ago number
22 let me give you a hand with all of
those
folders a fold the items carefully
B I really appreciate it C we gave the
performers a
hand number
23 what time did Mr Butters say he is
going to contact us a 5 days ago B I'll
get in contact C no later than seven
number
24 weren't we supposed to turn right at
the last
intersection a yes let's turn right here
B no at the next one c yeah the streets
intersect
here number
25 why can't we connect to the internet
right now A we're not connected to it B
there's a problem of some sorts
C I'll call the repairman
now number
26 has the shipment from Murray office
supplies arrived yet a it won't be here
until
tomorrow B several boxes of pens and
paper c not by ship but by
plane number 27
how many times this week has the machine
broken down a it's the latest model B
it's time to take a break C twice
according to my
count number 28 you ought to renew your
magazine subscription by
July a thanks for the reminder B it's a
daily
newspaper C yes I'm I read it every
month number 29 doesn't this contract
require three people's
signatures a yes yours and two other
individuals B sign on the dotted line
please C you're not required to sign
it number 30 do you mind taking a look
at this budget
form a we went over budget last month B
yes we are minding our own business C
can I do that after the
conference number
31 how did you enjoy your meal at the
Spanish
restaurant a it was a bit too spicy for
me B I look forward to trying the food
there C Jeff paid for everyone's
[Music]
meal number seven the files have all
been submitted haven't they a yes about
2 hours ago B I'll submit my application
then C Mr Peters wants to see
them number eight I recommend applying
for a job at hermine
Consulting a a low-level employee there
b that's what I'm planning to do c no
you didn't recommend
that no number nine how long do you
intend to wait for Mr
Schnell a I've known him for years B
several months from now C until the work
day
ends number 10 what time is the flight
supposed to
land a let me check the schedule B we're
landing in San
Francisco C it's flight TR
492 number 11 shouldn't you submit the
application form at once a actually I
already did B apply it to the
surface C yes he has very good
form number 12 do you happen to know who
the head accountant is
a he works in the accounting department
B get ahead by working hard C his name
is Fred
Marshall number
13 can you please file these documents
for me a there's the file cabinet B
sorry but I'm too busy now C no they
haven't been documented
number
14 where did Jenny put the stapler after
she finished using it a the Staples are
in the drawer B she left it on the
counter C I'm sitting at my desk
now number 15 how much does it cost to
purchase a box of
paper a I bought some paper B 5,000
sheets per box C I'm not quite
sure number
16 there appears to be a mistake on this
report a why am I mistaken B didn't he
report it C what's wrong with
it number number 17 could you please
send me the itinerary by
email a I'll do that after lunch B
that's my email address C it's our
schedule for the
conference number
18 why don't we meet Mr Richardson at
the restaurant after work a I'd like a
menu please B no he doesn't work there
C I already have plans
tonight number
19 was that Mr Murphy's boss who just
called him on the phone a his boss is
Miss thunderson B no it was a client of
his C call me at 4074994695
what's your opinion of that article on
the front
page a yes I'm reading it B I haven't
read it yet C he wrote a short
article number
21 when did Miss Jackson send the
contract to be signed a by Courier I
believe B both your name and hers C two
or 3 days ago
number
22 let me give you a hand with all of
those
folders a fold the items carefully B I
really appreciate it C we gave the
performers a
hand number
23 what time did Mr Butters say he is
going to contact us a 5 days ago B I'll
get in contact C no later than
seven number
24 weren't we supposed to turn right at
the last
intersection a yes let's turn right here
B no at the next one c yeah the streets
intersect here
number
25 why can't we connect to the internet
right now A we're not connected to it B
there's a problem of some sorts C I'll
call the repairman
now number
26 has the shipment from Murray office
supplies arrived yet a it won't be here
until tomorrow B several boxes of pens
and paper c not by ship but by
plane number
27 how many times this week has the
machine broken down a it's the latest
model B it's time to take a break C
twice according to my
count number 28
you ought to renew your magazine
subscription by
July a thanks for the reminder B it's a
daily
newspaper C yes I read it every
month number 29 doesn't this contract
require three people's
signatures a yes yours and two other
individuals B sign on the dotted line
please
C you're not required to sign
it number 30 do you mind taking a look
at this budget
form a we went over budget last month B
yes we are minding our own business C
can I do that after the
conference number
31 how did you enjoy your meal at the
Spanish
restaurant a it was a bit too spicy for
me B I look forward to trying the food
there see Jeff paid for everyone's meal